





WHO AM I?

Hello, my name is Tom Konidas and I'm a minimalist who truly believes that less is more. I specialize in the MERN stack and believe in the TDD ethos. My passions are Software Development, Cybersecurity, Free and Open Source Software and the communities that surround them. I love knowledge and I strongly believe technology can, and should, enrich every single life our universe has to offer. I am currently studying for my CCNA. Wish me luck!

ReactJS	
NodeJS/Express	
Typescript/JS(ES6)	
REST/GraphQL	
SQL/NoSQL	
Jest Testing Framework	
GNU/Linux/Bash	

EXPERIENCE

1/2019 - Present

Full-Stack Developer

Fix Network

Developed an internal e-commerce platform.

Developed & designed an internal careers admin page connecting all the umbrella brands.

Created custom software and tools to better help employees and franchisees.

Generated automatic reports querying large data for helpful insights.

Maintained public corporate sites for over 500 shops worldwide.

Sncode / Extenso / MariaDB / jQuery / Bootstrap / Git

1/2018 - 12/2018 Full Time

Application Support Analyst

Tecsys Inc.

Improved database performance using SolarWinds, JavaMelody and Nagios.

Applied patches to large codebase and installed on all customers' environments.

Obtained 'Pat on the back' award from customer for going beyond and beyond my responsibilities. Reproduced bugs and logged tickets to R&D.

Provided on-site support for customers.

Java / MS SQL / SCRUM / SVN

9/2017 - 12/2017 Internship

Engineering/Marketing

Ranger Design

Hired as the link between Engineering and Marketing to work on the Ranger Design Configurator. Optimized Meshes in Rhino5/Blender decreasing load times on the website.

Created and edited CAD layouts in Solidworks helping customers visualize their custom orders. Documented product changes within ERP (Infor SyteLine).

Blender / SolidWorks / Rhino5

1/2015 - 5/2015 Internship

Full-Stack Developer

Booxi

Developed an admin panel (CRUD) using Google's Web Toolkit (GWT) and python back-end. Coded web-scraping scripts (Python BeautifulSoup Library) gathering potential customers. Contributed to large codebase and learned how to work with git repositories within a team.

Java / Python / MySQL / REST / GWT / Git

EDUCATION

2012 - 2015

DEC in Computer Science & Technology

Vanier College

LANGUAGES

English - native French - proficient Greek - rudimentary

HOBBIES

Trying new GNU/Linux distros. Discovering new podcasts and listening/viewing to conference talks. Producing music,videos and graphic art. Keeping up to date with FOSS and Hacker culture.

NON PROFIT

I help run the Montreal Elixir Meetup by recording the talks and edit/post them online.